<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Live Cricket TV Match Score</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_player_information">PlayerInformation</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="text_only">ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijlkmnopqrstuvwxyz</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="pred_wizrddetails">Our \"Prediction Wizard\" will calculate, based on the current available betting odds, the implicit winning percentages for the possible outcomes in a match. This will be updated as soon as we fetch the odds from the betting sites and keep updating until the match is finished.</string>
    <string name="opendrawer">Open</string>
    <string name="closedrawer">Close</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Live Cricket TV &amp; Scores allow users to Catch all the action ball by ball, starting with the toss of course. Know the milestones and the innings, the controversies, and the biggest hitters and bowlers. But that is not all. Know the history of the game and the players’ names, the important global competitions. Get interested in records too. Get everything cricket at your fingertips wherever you go on the phone.  Live Cricket TV &amp; Scores interest everybody, the experts and the beginners. Start a new interest. Play cricket physically or online. Know all the trending news and analysis by the experts just as they happen. What are the matches coming up soon, and when and where? You need to know quite a bit really.  Everybody needs a passion that starts as a passing interest. Exciting Live Cricket TV &amp; Scores allows lots of adjustments to reflect the individual personality. Choose between light and dark themes. Customize the live score widgets. Share with family and friends. The points table is always ready.  Key features:  -Live ball-by-ball scoreboard keeps you up to date -Previous match results and upcoming match schedules -Expert analysis for a thorough understanding -Graphical user interface is spellbinding -KnowRankings for bowlers, batsmen, all-rounders, and teams  How to use it?  The first step is to download the Live Cricket TV &amp; Scores app at the online Play Store. Choose from the available apps but keep the compatibility with the Android phone version in mind. The app version and the phone’s Android version should match. After the free and fast download, study the app and its features. Launch the activities and never stop enjoying the game.  Entertaining Live Cricket TV &amp; Scores wows you with so many features to blow your mind. Cricket is everywhere and so are the fans. Choose your favourite players and join the conversation on social media. Enjoy the news and interviews. Watch hundreds of hours of recorded cricket content. Match video highlights are super. Enjoy each moment. Match previews and statistics are very informative.  Disclaimer:  We don\'t own any content that we are using in our app. All rights are reserved by their respective owners. We are only providing facility to sports lovers and we don\'t have any other means with this app. In case of any problem please contact us directly and we will cooperate with you fully.  Live Cricket TV &amp; Scores HD does not tolerate any copyright infringement on the site. It is our policy to respond to clear notices of alleged copyright infringement. If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof, and you believe that any content on this app has objectionable content or violates your copyrights, please contact us by mail Those content will be permanently removed!</string>
    <string name="special_case">By pressing the Accept button, I declare I have read and accepted the following condition of use:</string>
</resources>